<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Anila_1202150280_Modul3</string>
    <string name="title_placeholder">Title</string>
    <string name="news_label">News</string>
    <string name="aqua_info_placeholder">Here is some news</string>
    <string name="ades_image">Ades Image</string>
    <string name="filler_text"></string>

    <string-array name="aqua_titles">
        <item>ADES</item>
        <item>AMIDIS</item>
        <item>AQUA</item>
        <item>CLEO</item>
        <item>CLUB</item>
        <item>EQUIL</item>
        <item>EVIAN</item>
        <item>LEMINERALE</item>
        <item>NESTLE</item>
        <item>PRISTINE</item>
        <item>VIT</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="aqua_info">
        <item>About ADES</item>
        <item>About AMIDIS</item>
        <item>About AQUA</item>
        <item>About CLEO</item>
        <item>About CLUB</item>
        <item>About EQUIL</item>
        <item>About EVIAN</item>
        <item>About LEMINERALE</item>
        <item>About NESTLE</item>
        <item>About PRISTINE</item>
        <item>About VIT</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="aqua_images">
        <item>@drawable/ades</item>
        <item>@drawable/amidis</item>
        <item>@drawable/aqua</item>
        <item>@drawable/cleo</item>
        <item>@drawable/club</item>
        <item>@drawable/equil</item>
        <item>@drawable/evian</item>
        <item>@drawable/leminerale</item>
        <item>@drawable/nestle</item>
        <item>@drawable/pristine</item>
        <item>@drawable/vit</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="detail_titles">
        <item> AdeS is a brand of drinking water available in Indonesia.
        The mineral water is also known as I-Lohas in Japan. </item>
        <item>AMIDIS adalah produk Air Minum Dalam Kemasan (AMDK) yang sudah diproduksi sejak tahun 1997 dan
            merupakan air minum distilasi pertama di Indonesia
        </item>
        <item>AQUA Group menerapkan nilai-nilai Danone Group, yang menggambarkan visi dan etika binis kami yang unik.
            Sejarah nilai-nilai ini mencerminkan komitmen perusahaan kami terhadap komunikasi yang terbuka dan kerja bersama.
          </item>
        <item>Air murni terasa lebih ringan (light), tidak berasa bila diminum dan tubuh akan menjadi segar sesudah meminumnya.
            Air murni tidak mengandung bakteri, virus, dan mineral anorganik. </item>
        <item>Club is the brand name for a series of Irish carbonated soft drinks produced in Ireland by
            Britvic Ireland and previously by Cantrell Cochrane (CC). </item>
        <item>EQUIL  was first bottled in 1998 at the source, Villa D’Equilibrium, and launched to the market which was
            then predominantly monopolized by few European brands.</item>
        <item>Evian is a brand of mineral water coming from several sources near Évian-les-Bains, on the south shore of Lake Geneva.</item>
        <item>Le Minerale, pure and preserved mineral water sourced from the mountain and packed directly on site using the latest
            technology (mineral protection system) to bring you a healthy refreshment for optimum body function.</item>
        <item>Nestlé is the world’s largest food and beverage company. We have more than 2000 brands ranging from global icons to local favourites,
            and we are present in 189 countries around the world.</item>
        <item>Water as the most important part and can not be detached from the life of living creatures in this world.
           </item>
        <item>stay hydrated while you enhance your water drinking experience with the vitamins and
            electrolytes in the many flavors of vitaminwater®. try a bottle today!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
